(Episode 7)
I'm not sure if he's a good person or not.
But he likes me a lot.
I haven't had anyone
who liked me for a long time,
besides you.
You and Yu Mi look great together.
So I want to be happy like you are.
Will you be happy for me?
I'll appreciate it
if you support Director Han.
He is still young,
and has a lot to learn on the job.
- By the way.
- What is it?
Why is the food always bad?
Do you really think it's tasty?
He's the youngest son...
All right now, can we start?
They say reservations for public courses
have decreased.
Speaking of which...
What? Are you not satisfied with
the desserts, either?
The public courses
have more female members.
So, how about we offer exclusive benefits
for female members?
Such as giving priority to them...
and arranging teams
based on their levels and ages.
Since men often go golfing for business,
they don't have much trouble
having their teams.
But I think it is probably a challenge
to make teams for housewives.
I briefly pointed out problems
with our course menu.
Especially,
about this unpleasant main dish.
Many complaints are saying
our menu selection is not good enough.
I believe it is a big issue at a golf club
where people invite their guests.
Please look at the first page.
What?
You did a good job. What happened?
I need to do things properly...
to support my family.
Aren't you getting on?
See you later.
What did you mean?
What was that about?
Is it Eun Seo? Is it?
See you later.
Okay, all right.
I'm coming today.
Eun Seo?
Of course.
Yes.
See you later, then.
Stop laughing at me.
Wait and see.
Can you get the ball for me?
That one.
This is expensive, isn't it?
My mom told me one day.
Gifts shouldn't be judged by their value.
Give me that.
I'll put it on you.
I'll be good.
I'll be good to you. I will try.
I'll be the man you wish for.
I even attended the meeting today.
I did a great job.
I am sorry.
I can't take this.
I have nothing for you,
so I shouldn't take this.
I know that.
I'll take care of everything.
You just stay.
You just breathe, smile, and...
just stay by my side.
Will you?
Yes?
How have you been?
Do you think I would've been good?
I don't want your apology.
Have you lost trust in me that much?
Yes, I have.
If you're sorry,
would you go somewhere with me?
Come on in.
Would you like a coffee?
This is my apartment.
I moved a few days ago.
I didn't get the best one,
since I was in a rush.
It is a fine place, isn't it?
It's close to your studio and school.
Yu Mi.
I know what you want to say.
I know you don't love me,
and you've never loved me.
So, as you said,
it would be better for me
to break up with you.
I'm not a fool. I know everything.
I have something I haven't told you.
I like someone else.
I even know why you are...
so cruel to me.
You're trying to make me give up on you.
But, I have no intention to leave you.
Even if you love someone else,
I don't want to let you go.
Does the person, whom you like,
like you back?
If I let you go,
can you marry her?
Is there any chance for that?
Yu Mi, she...
It's probably Tae Seok and Eun Seo.
I invited them for dinner.
They are seeing each other now.
You don't know that, do you?
It looks great.
When did you do all of this?
It's been about a week.
It must've been a lot of work.
Congratulations on your new home.
Thanks.
Do you like it here, Eun Seo?
It is a pretty apartment.
Have a seat.
The dinner will be ready soon.
It's not a lot, but help yourself.
There is a lot of food.
Do you want to try this?
Do you know how to eat?
I'm fine.
Try it.
Do you like it?
Jun Seo, did she eat well like this
as a child?
She did.
I think she was adorable.
Jun Seo, I'm jealous of you.
You saw her so much when she was little.
Since you grew up together,
you two are like real siblings, I believe.
You probably feel like she is your sister
more than Sin Ae is.
I like that.
Do you mean this one?
It is pretty, isn't it?
I found it for her.
Did you find it? I see.
I wanted to give her a ring,
but I think it's too early.
Check out mine, first.
Then, you get her a better one
than my ring, Tae Seok.
Is this your engagement ring?
Do you like it?
Yes, it is beautiful.
Jun Seo, you have good taste.
Jun Seo, you should choose our ring later.
I'll get you more soup.
It's hot!
Are you all right? Did you burn yourself?
No.
Did you make up with Jun Seo?
He is stubborn.
He will be better soon.
Are you happy, Eun Seo?
Tae Seok is a good guy
if you get to know him better.
I know.
I bet you were so adorable
when you were little.
I don't remember that much.
Do you remember about Jun Seo?
Yes.
Of course, I remember him.
She was pretty.
She was really pretty.
How lucky you are.
You have so many memories with Eun Seo.
I'm envious of you for the first time.
I officially ask your permission.
Please allow me.
I'll make your cousin happy.
Jun Seo.
Tae Seok, I have something to tell you...
I'm asking you, too.
Please make Eun Seo happy.
Do you allow me on behalf of Jun Seo?
Since you two will get married soon?
Eun Seo.
We should stop lying.
I don't want to lie anymore.
If we're not honest now,
we will all be miserable.
It'll be much harder later on.
Tae Seok, you, me, and Yu Mi,
all of us.
You're not in love with him.
Do you really love Tae Seok?
You don't, Eun Seo.
I think this is it.
We should've called them before we came.
Dad.
Mom?
Eun Seo?
Eun Seo.
Let me look at you.
- Are you Eun Seo?
- Yes, mom.
- Eun Seo?
- Mom.
Eun Seo.
- Eun Seo.
Are you Eun Seo? Eun Seo?
Eun Seo, you have grown up.
Mom.
You have grown up so much.
While you have grown up this much,
I haven't done anything for you.
Hasn't it been hard, Eun Seo?
No, it hasn't.
How were you at school?
I was fine.
But I wasn't a great student.
Mom, I'm sorry.
You know I didn't like studying.
Eun Seo, what should I do?
I'm so sorry, Eun Seo.
I left you alone,
I left you behind...
It's okay, Mom. I'm fine.
What is wrong with me?
I should stop crying.
I can't see your face
with tears in my eyes, can I?
Did you miss me a lot?
How much did you miss me?
You didn't forget me, did you?
I...
I was sick because I missed you so much.
I was very sick
because I miss you so much.
I couldn't come back because I was sick.
Eun Seo.
My Eun Seo.
She grew up so well.
She is beautiful. Gorgeous.
Yes.
So, does she work at a hotel?
Yes, Dad.
She raised her well.
She did raise her better
than I ever expected.
It was my mistake.
I made a big mistake.
We should've taken care of Eun Seo,
no matter what.
When your mom was too sick to travel,
I should've come to take her to the U.S.
Dad,
It's fine.
She grew up well.
Eun Seo grew up really well.
You are right.
She grew up so well.
I'm grateful.
Thank her so much for that.
Mom?
Mom.
- Dad.
- Yes.
You could've called me,
I would have gone to Seoul to pick you up.
All the way to Seoul from here?
It wasn't necessary.
Sin Ae.
Mom.
Yes.
What is all that in the garden?
We thought of having lunch together
since it's been a long time.
For real? That's great.
It's perfect because I'm so hungry.
What is wrong, Mom?
- You.
- Yes?
Why didn't you tell us you met Eun Seo?
We are home.
Didn't it take too long, Eun Seo?
Sin Ae.
You two also haven't met each other
for a long time, have you?
Sin Ae, hear me out.
- Sin Ae.
Yoon Sin Ae.
You are all here.
I heard you are having a family gathering.
I guess I deserve to join it now.
What is it?
Did someone hit her?
Who hit her?
So, this makes 29 votes for Yoon Eun Seo
and 16 votes for Choi Sin Ae.
Our class president
for the second semester is Yoon Eun Seo.
Do not touch Eun Seo's clothes.
Eun Seo!
Bye.
Come here.
What are you doing?
Why do you always behave like this?
What did you touch?
What a temper you have.
What did you just touch?
What did you put your hand on?
Stop there.
I am sorry. I am...
Sin Ae.
Stop it.
No, I'm not crying.
I'm not.
I'm not crying.
Please stop crying.
Have they treated you well?
Haven't they scolded you too much?
Have they been good to you?
They have treated me well.
Of course, they have. I am their daughter.
I had everything I ever wanted.
Thank you.
I'm so grateful.
Thanks.
That's enough. It's so upsetting.
Why are we like this?
Eun Seo is happy to meet her mother,
but why are we like this?
Eun Seo...
Did Eun Seo meet her mom?
Did she?
- I'll get mom here.
- Yes.
Everyone is waiting for you.
What about Sin Ae?
Why did you do that?
It hurts Sin Ae.
Whether I raised Sin Ae well or not,
I had her with me.
I have taken care of her,
although I couldn't do my best
because I was sick.
I have raised her.
But Eun Seo...
Jun Seo.
You love Eun Seo, don't you?
Do you care for her as you did before?
I do.
When she was born, we named her Eun Seo.
And we were happy to imagine
that people would think...
you were loving siblings
when they found out your names...
were Jun Seo and Eun Seo.
Just like your names,
I was picturing that...
you live happily with me forever.
You have no idea how happy I was.
Jun Seo.
You can't leave Eun Seo alone.
You need to care for her...
and take care of her forever
as your sister.
Will you, Jun Seo?
Please answer me.
Promise me.
Yes.
Eun Seo, help yourself.
I made only your favorites.
Is that true?
Then, I will eat them all.
Are you guys that serious already?
I would like to ask your daughter
to marry me.
I will make her happy.
Have you already grown up that much?
But, Jun Seo and Yu Mi
have to get married first.
I have a camera.
Would you like to take some pictures?
Smile.
Get ready now.
One.
You and Yu Mi look great together.
So I want to be happy like you are.
Do you really love Tae Seok?
You don't, Eun Seo.
When she was born,
we named her Eun Seo. And we were happy...
to imagine that people would think
you were loving siblings...
when they found out
your names were Jun Seo and Eun Seo.
Jun Seo.
You can't leave Eun Seo alone.
You need to care for her...
and take care of her forever
as your sister.
Will you, Jun Seo?
Yes, I admit you're pretty.
I didn't say otherwise. Yu Mi.
Mister.
You call me "mister."
That's why I said you're not pretty.
All right, you win. Ji Hwan.
Okay, so pretty.
Yu Mi is pretty.
You, mister.
You called me mister, again.
What is so funny?
Jun Seo.
One is Jun Seo, and the other is mister.
All right, whatever.
Mom and Dad haven't changed at all.
Right?
You haven't changed, either.
Look at this grumpy face.
What did you say?
I've been thinking about...
what I would have been left with
if I hadn't had you.
I believe I would have nothing left.
I would, too.
Me too, Jun Seo.
Eun Seo.
Because of you, my life became...
so beautiful that it is incomparable.
Yes.
Let's stay together
for the rest of our lives.
As brother and sister.
Then, without betraying or hurting anyone,
we can be together forever.
For the rest of our lives.
Yoon Jun Seo, what brought you here?
Do you want to grab a drink?
What is happening? You can drink.
I'm sorry.
For what?
I'm sorry for having
such a beautiful cousin.
You like Eun Seo a lot, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Okay.
Are you worried?
What are you concerned about?
I'm not.
I just...
I wonder if you know how beautiful
Eun Seo is.
You should know that in full.
- I shouldn't know everything about her.
- What?
I'll take my time to get to know her,
so don't worry.
We have lots of time.
Yes, you have time.
But can I tell you something?
When Eun Seo gets upset,
she always laughs.
Right, you are right.
She laughs when she is upset,
which is scary.
When she sleeps,
she falls asleep against the wall.
Is that so?
And...
she says, "you are mean,"
and "thanks for the meal" while dining.
She has always had long hair,
since she was little.
She used to like making confessions.
She was so bad at sports.
Also, she whined a lot.
She was such a whiner.
I'm sorry.
Are you drunk?
You are drunk.
I can't believe Yoon Jun Seo got drunk.
One more thing.
It's the most important thing.
When Eun Seo plays Rock, Paper, Scissors,
she always makes a Rock, Tae Seok.
Really?
Rock, Paper, Scissors.
Why do I always make a Rock?
- Rock, Paper, Scissors.
- Wait.
I was overjoyed when you called.
I thought I was the only one
who called now.
Yu Mi.
I'm sorry.
What is wrong?
No, nothing.
I'll call you more often.
I'll call you before you do.
Jun Seo, have you made up your mind?
Did you decide to stay with me?
I'm sorry for hurting you.
I'm sorry.
I'm also sorry that...
all I can say is that
I'll continue to try harder.
If you would still like that...
I would like that, yes. I like it.
I like it, Jun Seo.
Eun Seo, would you like to stay with me?
What?
Ji Hwan said that...
the studio doesn't have enough space
since he expanded the work area.
Didn't Jun Seo tell you about it?
I see...
If you have nowhere to go,
you can stay in my apartment.
You should. Will you do that?
No, I think I'm all right.
I can go back to the staff accommodations.
To the staff accommodations?
To the staff accommodations? Really?
Then we can see each other
morning and night.
Tae Seok.
That's great.
It's a bit dangerous at night here.
I have also been worried
since this place isn't that comfortable.
Your brother's not much of a help.
Are you saying she's been a burden?
It would be great to leave
before you annoy him.
Yes, it's great.
Do you want to submit the application?
- Don't do that.
- Really?
Then, let's play Rock, Paper, Scissors.
No.
The staff accommodations, please.
What?
What do you mean my application
to the staff accommodations got canceled?
Don't you know that?
I received the list today.
I wonder if it's been decided
on short notice.
No, I had no idea.
I brought all my belongings today.
I need to get into staff accommodations.
I have nowhere to go.
If you are really desperate,
why don't you ask Director Han?
Don't get me wrong.
I'm saying it with good intention.
I'm sorry I was mistaken about you
and gave you a hard time.
Actually,
Director Han came to me the other day,
he told me he's getting married to you.
I think it would be best...
to ask Director Han.
Don't you believe me?
I really came to my senses.
Has Han Tae Seok finally settled?
I'll introduce you to her soon.
You have no idea how beautiful she is.
Quit just talking about it and set a date.
Mom.
What are you doing, mom?
Take this with you.
Mom?
I heard they came back to Korea.
If you stay with me,
you would end up living like me.
I'll pretend you got married and left.
I know they couldn't forget you,
and she has been sick.
It is an emotional journey
to raise someone.
So, go to them.
Mom, I'm sorry.
If you don't like it,
I won't meet them again.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Leave.
I did enough for you until now,
when I had nothing.
Why do you want to stay,
when I say you bother me?
My life would be much better
if it weren't for you.
I took and raised you so far
because you are my child.
But it's time for you to leave.
Live on your own now.
- Mom.
- Go.
Go to your real mom. Go.
- Mom.
- Go to your real mom.
- Go.
- Mom.
Mom.
Go.
You're not my daughter.
You're too much for me from the beginning.
Although it's late, study properly,
wear some nice clothes,
and don't look so grim
at such a young age.
What do you mean?
Why couldn't she get into
the staff accommodations?
Didn't she come to you?
- No, she didn't.
- She didn't?
She said she had nowhere to go.
Where did she go, then?
I think we'll be done by tomorrow
once we move some more.
It would be better for you
to find another studio.
I like it here. I'll work here.
- I'm leaving.
- All right, bye.
Jun Seo.
Eun Seo, what are you doing here?
I brought my stuff from home.
I'm heading to
the staff accommodations now.
I see.
I forgot something,
so I stopped by to pick it up.
Okay, come on in.
It's not here.
It's not. I came for no reason, then.
Is it not there?
I'll come by often.
Can I come often?
Of course.
I will, then.
I was going to leave
when you weren't here,
so I took my stuff when I went to work.
But I failed.
Eun Seo, is something wrong?
No, nothing's wrong.
It's getting late.
The staff accommodations will close soon.
I should get going.
Eun Seo.
Jun Seo.
Be nice to Yu Mi.
I'll be nice to Tae Seok,
and you'll do the same to Yu Mi.
Give it to me. I'll give you a ride.
Jun Seo.
Eun Seo.
Don't turn around.
Jun Seo.
We are brother and sister now, right?
Eun Seo.
When did you know?
Don't you think we are going against fate?
So what? What if we do?
It's my fate, too.
My fate is much more powerful.
I will show them that.
Marry me.
Marry me, Choi Eun Seo.
Eun Seo, is it Jun Seo you like?
Do you have a secret
that you can't say out loud?
- Stop it.
- You don't get to yell at me.
The secret.
Can I tell you what it is?
The secret is that you like Jun Seo.
Han Tae Seok.